Digital Media Department; Collection ua395
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Digital Media Department Records
1921-2016
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
ua395
12 GB
31.66 cubic ft.
This collection consists of both physical photographic materials and digital photography created by the campus photographer that documents the University at Albany, SUNY.
Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted.
Acquisition Information
Most Items in this collection prior to 2012 were transferred to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives by Mark Schmidt and Paul Miller of the Digital Media Department which is part of the Office of Communication and Marketing.
Most of the pre-2012 images were written to optical media (DVDs and some CD-Rs) by the University Photographer. Most of the images were raw camera files .NEF and .CR2 with altered derivatives created as JPG and a few TIFF files. Prior to accessioning, the archivist converted all raw camera images to JPG format and accepted only the original derivatives and the converted versions of files without derivatives.
Most of the images created after 2012 were downloaded 2015 July 19
Historical Note
The Digital Media Department is part of the Office of Communication and Marketing. They are charged with creating video and still images of the university and major events. Many of these items are created for marketing and other publications. The Department has also previously been known as both Creative Services and the Media and Marketing.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of both still photographs created digitally by the campus photographer and physical photographic prints, contact sheets and negatives. The materials in this collection are generally promotional in nature and appear to have been created for marketing purposes, providing an "official" view of campus events and activities.
Arrangement of the Collection
Material from the UAlbanyPhotos website was maintained in its original arrangement. If items were moved the new arrangement was also maintained, so there is the potential for duplication.
Material that was transferred on optical media were matched by job number found in the top level directory. This job number was matched to a database maintained by the University Photographer which included basic descriptions, the ordering department, and timestamps. For Images from 2010-2012, a newer database was used that did not include descriptions. Descriptions for these items came from the directory names that held the images.
The images transferred on optical media were matched by the archivist to the arrangement provided by the UAlbanyPhotos website. Physical photographic materials have also been added to this collection as their own series.
Digital Files; UAlbany Communications & Marketing; State University of New York at Albany. Office of Communication and Marketing
- Creative Services, 1921-2001; 26.66 cubic ft.
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of the materials the department produced and used before transitioning to the use of digital media. The materials in this series are from the period in which the department was known as Creative Services. Some photographic materials were created by the department while older materials in the series were produced elsewhere and retained by them for the creation of promotional material.
  The series includes photographsic prints, negatives, slides, contact sheets and VHS tapes. This series includes posed portraits, building photographs, and candids taken to document university events. Both color and black and white materials can be found in this series. Some materials contain exact dates or years, but many of the materials were previously unlabelled and have been given approximate dates. Some photographs and negative sleeves include a numerical value similar to a job number written on them, in which case that number has been retained.
  Arrangement
  Materials in this series were maintained in their original shelf order. Photograpic material make up one sub-series while photographic materials make up the other.
  - Video Materials, 1973-1998; 1.66 cubic ft.
    Materials have been arranged chronologically.
    This collection is made up of video materials documenting the history of the University. This series includes recordings of University Senate meetings, convocations, dedications and other campus and community events related to the University and Albany more broadly.
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    This series includes VHS tapes, audiocassettes and reel-to-reel tapes which need proper media viewers in order to be used.
  - Photographic Materials, 1921-2001; 25 cubic ft.
    Materials have been maintained in their original shelf order.
    This sub-series is made up of the photographic materials in the Creative Services series. It consists of contact sheets, negatives and photographic prints. Also includes a largely complete alphabetical series of faculty portraits from the period of 1991-1997.
    - Unidentified Faculty Portraits on Posterboard as pre-prints for publication, ca. 1985 (Flat-file 1)
      Immediate Source of Acquisition
      Stamped "Received August 30, 2006."
- University Graphics Photographic Materials, 1974-1991; 5 cubic ft.
  Materials in this series are arranged alphabetically by subject.
  This series is made up of negatives, contact sheets, and a small amount of photographic prints produced by University Graphics. Materials in this series appear to have been produced for promotional purposes and were likely created for use by the Office of Communications and Marketing and its predecessors.
- Born-Digital Photographs, 1999-2019
  Material from the UAlbanyPhotos website was maintained in its original arrangement. If items were moved the new arrangement was also maintained, so there is the potential for duplication.
  Material that was transferred on optical media were matched by job number found in the top level directory. This job number was matched to a database maintained by the University Photographer which included basic descriptions, the ordering department, and timestamps. For Images from 2010-2012, a newer database was used that did not include descriptions. Descriptions for these items came from the directory names that held the images.
  The images transferred on optical media were matched by the archivist to the arrangement provided by the UAlbanyPhotos website.
  This series consists of photographs created digitally by the campus photographer. The materials in this series are generally promotional in nature and appear to have been created for marketing purposes, providing an "official" view of campus events and activities. Subjects include athletic teams, campus buildings, campus events, portraits of students, faculty and alumni, and university-organized events that took place off-campus.
  - Academics, 2007 December 5-2016 July 17; 1; 4367 Digital Files
    - Academics, 2007 December 5-2016 July 17; 1.1; 4367 Digital Files
      - Criminal Justice: Graduate Program in Criminal Justice Poster 11 x 17, 2000 October 24; 6.3 MB 10 Digital Files
        2016 December 14 17:15:55 Accession: ua395-CsBH9SJr2w5jHtUHPFrooF
        2016 December 14 Imaged from optical media with dd, carved from image with fiwalk and icat, converted all raw to jpg
        2016 December 14 description record extracted from photographer's Microsoft Access database by Job number
      - EOP: 4/18/01 @ 10:30 AM BA 212 classroom digital, 2001 May 1; 30.9 MB 25 Digital Files
      - EOP: 4/18/01 @ 2 PM EOP various situations digital, 2001 May 1; 22.7 MB 19 Digital Files
      - Education: 2/4/02 @ 1:30 PM Husted 167 George Litchford w/ student digital, 2002 February 13; 26.5 MB 21 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 2/19/02 @ 10 AM Accelerator Lab Bill Lanford and Thomas Huthwelker digital, 2002 March 1; 29.7 MB 26 Digital Files
      - Ctr. For Autism and Related Disorders: 3/11/02 @ 6:30 PM East Campus / Sch. Of Pub Health Dr. Mark Durand w/class digital, 2002 March 12; 83.5 MB 34 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 4/12/02 @ 9:15 AM Chem 222 group photo in lab digital, 2002 April 26; 34.2 MB 32 Digital Files
      - Physics: 4/19/02 @ 3 PM PAC - Flutterer Lounge reception and lecture for Wolfgang Ketterle - Nobel Prize in Physics digital, 2002 May 3; 79.6 MB 66 Digital Files
      - Education: 6/5/02 @ 9:30 AM CC Ballroom Digital Divide Conference digital image, 2002 June 19; 63.0 MB 43 Digital Files
      - Public Health: 7/23/02 @ 8 AM Rensselaerville Institute Rensselaerville, NY Team building sessions digital, 2002 August 7; 79.0 MB 40 Digital Files
      - Public Health: 8/13/02 @ 10:30 AM School of Public Health East Campus Community Outreach Retreat digital, 2002 August 28; 21.1 MB 18 Digital Files
      - School of Public Health: various for view book, 2002 September 30; 20.0 MB 13 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 10/24/02 @ 2:30 PM Clifton Park, NY Jennifer Toscano / Online Classroom digital, 2002 November 7; 95.9 MB 36 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 11/21/02 @ 4 PM BA-349 Prof. Peter Ross and Students digital, 2002 December 5; 14.5 MB 13 Digital Files
      - UAIM: 1/16/03 @ 2 PM Shadi Shahedipour's Lab Room Photo digital, 2003 January 28; 244.1 MB 106 Digital Files
      - Outreach: 2/11/03 @ 1 PM Studio / Bio B-11 Prof. John Schmidt w/ faculty and students studio groupings and lab shot, 2003 February 25; 245.6 MB 93 Digital Files
      - Outreach: 2/13/03 @ 8:45 AM Developmental Pediatrics / Latham, NY Gail Landsman w/ doctor and paitients digital, 2003 February 27; 260.5 MB 97 Digital Files
      - Outreach: 2/28/03 @ 12:30 PM East Campus A-wing Rm: 203 Peter Levin and David Strogatz digital, 2003 March 12; 14.3 MB 34 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 3/12/03 @ 3 PM Biology Sloan Foundation Award Recipient: Ing-Nang Wang digital, 2003 March 20; 11.9 MB 33 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 3/12/03 @ 9 AM Physics Susan Lee and Carolyn MacDonald w/grad student digital, 2003 March 24; 14.4 MB 37 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 10/10/03 @ 9 AM SS-116 Catherine Bertini w/ students in classroom digital, 2003 October 22; 104.3 MB 81 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 10/10/03 @ 9 AM SS-116 Catherine Bertini w/ students in classroom digital, 2003 October 22; 104.3 MB 81 Digital Files
      - Education: 11/5/03 @ 1:45 PM ED 212 Dean Susan Phillips w/ faculty in office digital, 2003 November 18; 91.7 MB 64 Digital Files
      - Education: 11/5/03 @ 1:45 PM ED 212 Dean Susan Phillips w/ faculty in office digital, 2003 November 18; 91.7 MB 64 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 12/15/03 @ 3:10 PM Draper 221 Jessica Landin and Lauren Mendolera in Jim Acker's class digital, 2003 December 26; 154.3 MB 44 Digital Files
      - African Studies: 3/11/04 @ 12 Noon BA 119 Dedication Ceremony and reception digital, 2004 March 19; 94.0 MB 82 Digital Files
      - African Studies: 3/11/04 @ 12 Noon BA 119 Dedication Ceremony and reception digital, 2004 March 19; 94.0 MB 82 Digital Files
      - Criminal Justice: photo shoot: 4/29/04 @ 1 PM Draper 219 viewbook photography digital, 2004 May 5; 181.4 MB 127 Digital Files
        2016 December 15 15:47:20 Accession: ua395-DpdVWtrwppUpJur3vAWnBU
        2016 December 15 Imaged from optical media with dd, carved from image with fiwalk and icat, converted all raw to jpg
        2016 December 15 description record extracted from photographer's Microsoft Access database by Job number
      - President: photo session: 5/7/04 @ 3:30 - 6:30 PM CC Ballroom KRH Farewell, 2004 May 8; 95.5 MB 63 Digital Files
        2016 December 14 description record used original folder name
      - President: photo session: 5/7/04 @ 3:30 - 6:30 PM CC Ballroom KRH Farewell, 2004 May 8; 145.3 MB 90 Digital Files
      - President: photo session: 5/7/04 @ 3:30 - 6:30 PM CC Ballroom KRH Farewell, 2004 May 8; 55.4 MB 33 Digital Files
      - President: photo session: 5/7/04 @ 3:30 - 6:30 PM CC Ballroom KRH Farewell, 2004 May 8; 95.6 MB 59 Digital Files
      - President: photo session: 5/7/04 @ 3:30 - 6:30 PM CC Ballroom KRH Farewell, 2004 May 8; 95.5 MB 63 Digital Files
      - President: photo session: 5/7/04 @ 3:30 - 6:30 PM CC Ballroom KRH Farewell, 2004 May 8; 52.2 MB 31 Digital Files
      - President: photo session: 5/7/04 @ 3:30 - 6:30 PM CC Ballroom KRH Farewell, 2004 May 8; 145.3 MB 90 Digital Files
      - President: photo session: 5/7/04 @ 3:30 - 6:30 PM CC Ballroom KRH Farewell, 2004 May 8; 55.4 MB 33 Digital Files
      - President: photo session: 5/7/04 @ 3:30 - 6:30 PM CC Ballroom KRH Farewell, 2004 May 8; 95.6 MB 59 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 5/5/04 @ 10:20 PAC 262 Auditioning class finals digital, 2004 May 19; 120.2 MB 28 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 5/5/04 @ 10:20 PAC 262 Auditioning class finals digital, 2004 May 19; 120.2 MB 28 Digital Files
      - Academic Support Services: 10/8/04 @ 2 PM EOP offices Project Excel digital, 2004 July 13; 194.5 MB 127 Digital Files
      - Education: 7/15/04 @ 9:15 AM location TBA STEP program w/ Joe Bowman and Albany City School Children Robotics class digital, 2004 July 28; 216.3 MB 134 Digital Files
      - Education: 7/22/04 @ 11 AM CETL / Science Library NYS Trustees visiting Joe Bowman's STEP program digital, 2004 August 5; 103.8 MB 66 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 9/29/04 @ 3:30 PM East Campus young scientists digital, 2004 October 7; 47.5 MB 31 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 10/5/04 @ 2 PM SS-221 Cheryl Frye and Kassandra Edinger digital, 2004 October 19; 197.3 MB 120 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 10/19/04 @ 3 PM LC-18 Judith Johnson's class / Foundations of Great Ideas student presentations digital, 2004 November 2; 52.0 MB 45 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 10/28/04 @ 2:30 PM CC Ballroom Pres. Ryan's Fall Faculty Speech digital, 2004 November 3; 51.3 MB 39 Digital Files
      - Education: 11/15/04 @ 10 AM ED-115 portrait: Miriam Raider-Roth digital, 2004 November 18; 89.8 MB 72 Digital Files
      - Criminal Justice: 12/8/04 @ 3:30 PM Standish Room/Science Library Former President Vince O'Leary Booksigning digital, 2004 December 8; 132.0 MB 84 Digital Files
        2016 December 15 09:03:03 Accession: ua395-h592ugDm48SamDdDr4w7TS
      - EOP: 12/21/04 @ 1:30 PM studio, 2004 December 29; 15.3 MB 12 Digital Files
      - Ctr for Women in Gov't & Civil Society: 1/21/05 @ 2:45 PM Draper 105 individual portraits & group shot / Fellows digital, 2005 January 25; 309.4 MB 157 Digital Files
      - Criminal Justice: 4/28/05 @ 12:15 PM Location TBA Criminal Justice Symposium Luncheon digital, 2005 March 30; 188.5 MB 120 Digital Files
      - Criminal Justice: 4/29/05 @ 5 PM Location TBA Criminal Justice Symposium Closing Cocktail Reception digital, 2005 March 30; 177.1 MB 126 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 4/11/05 @ 5:30 PM Alumni House George DeLuca w/ students; graduate exams digital, 2005 April 21; 182.7 MB 75 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 4/14/05 @ 10:30 AM Chem 336 / 335 Christopher Wells digital, 2005 April 25; 49.5 MB 31 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 4/13/05 @ 11:30 AM Pres Office Check presentation: Melanie Hansen digital, 2005 April 26; 24.8 MB 13 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 4/14/05 @ 8:30 AM University Club 141 Washington Ave. Albany, NY Pres Hall speaking digital, 2005 April 26; 67.6 MB 45 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 4/26/05 @ 9:45 AM RACC Pres Hall arriving in hydrogen/electric car to help with spring clean up. Digital, 2005 April 26; 104.4 MB 58 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 4/12/05 @ 4:15 PM LC-12 Pres Hall teaching in Sue Faerman's class digital, 2005 April 26; 33.9 MB 22 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 4/13/05 @ 11:30 AM Pres Office Check presentation: Melanie Hansen digital, 2005 April 26; 24.8 MB 13 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 4/14/05 @ 8:30 AM University Club 141 Washington Ave. Albany, NY Pres Hall speaking digital, 2005 April 26; 67.6 MB 45 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 4/27/05 @ 2:30 PM CC Ballroom President's Speech to Faculty digital, 2005 April 27; 142.6 MB 96 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 4/18/05 @ 3 PM Bio 318 Caro-Beth Stewart and Edgardo Sosa digital, 2005 May 2; 61.1 MB 48 Digital Files
      - Criminal Justice: 6/9/05 @ TBA Science Library / CETL room 2 Piyusha Singh's workshop on crime mapping for police officers digital, 2005 June 22; 46.5 MB 31 Digital Files
      - Public Health: 7/18/05 @ Noon - 4 PM Rensselaerville Institue Rensselaerville, NY Northeast Regional Public Health Leadership Institute digital, 2005 July 19; 287.7 MB 197 Digital Files
      - Biology: 7/14/05 @ 9:30 AM Life Science Bldg - various locations general lab shots digital, 2005 July 28; 234.1 MB 152 Digital Files
      - President: 7/20/05 @ 8:30 AM - 9:30 AM School of Public Health Auditorium - East Campus Integrating Genetics into Public Health and Healthcare digital, 2005 July 29; 84.2 MB 51 Digital Files
      - President: 7/20/05 @ 2:30 PM - 2:45 PM Library LC25 Pre-Freshman Summer Program digital, 2005 July 29; 35.5 MB 23 Digital Files
      - President: 7/26/05 @ 10:30 AM Bruno Cancer Center - East Campus Tour w/Sen. Bruno and Pres. Hall digital, 2005 July 29; 237.6 MB 157 Digital Files
      - Chemistry: 7/27/05 @ 11 AM Chemistry Bldg. Forensics lab shot digital, 2005 August 10; 153.0 MB 103 Digital Files
      - Chemistry: make Tif images/scans of book selections: 19 total, 2005 September 7; 69.2 MB 20 Digital Files
      - Rockefeller College: 11/4/05 @ various times Draper 2nd Fl Career Day / College of Computing and Information and the School of Criminal Justice digital, 2005 September 29; 150.0 MB 121 Digital Files
      - President: 11/8/05 @ 9:30 AM ED 335 Education & Counseling Psychology meeting digital, 2005 November 16; 43.4 MB 16 Digital Files
      - Ctr for Women in Government & Civil Society: 1/13/06 @ 1:15 PM Draper 105 head shots / group shot: 10 - 11 persons, 2006 January 24; 224.1 MB 40 Digital Files
      - Corporate and Foundation Relations: 1/13/06 @ 9:30 AM Cancer Research Center / GenNYsis East Campus various lab shots, 2006 January 26; 429.4 MB 229 Digital Files
      - Chemistry: 2/6/06 @ 11 AM Chemistry TBA various locations for brochure images, 2006 February 13; 430.1 MB 228 Digital Files
      - President: 1/31/06 @ 8:45 AM President's Office President for a Day, 2006 February 13; 61.9 MB 25 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 2/3/06 @ 9:30 AM Downtown Campus President Hall cutting down Sign, 2006 February 13; 45.6 MB 17 Digital Files
      - Ctr for Women in Government: 2/1/06 @ 3 PM Outside Draper Hall on Washington Ave. Liberty Partnership HS students and Univ. Minority Health Disparities project leave for tour of health facilities in Arbor Hill, 2006 February 13; 129.3 MB 17 Digital Files
      - President: President Hall's trip to China 12/05, 2006 February 14; 85.2 MB 40 Digital Files
      - Tom Walker, 2006 March 17; 324.4 MB 147 Digital Files
        2016 December 15 description record used original folder name
      - President: 3/7/06 @ 9 AM GenNYSis Board Room East Campus Board of Visitors, 2006 March 17; 61.0 MB 15 Digital Files
      - Elana Gordis, 2006 March 21; 208.5 MB 99 Digital Files
      - Igor Lednev, 2006 March 23; 104.4 MB 53 Digital Files
      - Lee Bickmore, 2006 March 23; 130.7 MB 62 Digital Files
      - Susan Gauss, 2006 March 24; 115.5 MB 56 Digital Files
      - George Levesque, 2006 March 29; 138.6 MB 58 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: various times and locations photos for Undergraduate Research Brochure / Mentoring Program, 2006 March 29; 377.4 MB 183 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 4/5/06 @ 6:15 PM A/S 104 Anthropology class / Guatemala, 2006 April 5; 90.3 MB 38 Digital Files
      - President: 3/22/06 @ 9:30 AM Science Library basement Albany HS student / first day, 2006 April 5; 99.4 MB 49 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 4/28/06 @ 8:30 AM Life Science 2094 and 2:30 PM Life Science 2101 Honors Conference, 2006 May 11; 11.6 MB 6 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 4/28/06 @ 8:30 AM Life Science 2094 and 2:30 PM Life Science 2101 Honors Conference, 2006 May 11; 13.3 MB 7 Digital Files
      - Advancement: 5/25/06 @ 2:30 PM Cancer Center - East Campus various lab shots, 2006 June 13; 286.2 MB 156 Digital Files
      - Public Health: 7/18/06 @ 12:30 PM Rensselaerville Institute Rensselaerville, NY School of Public Health Retreat, 2006 July 24; 283.1 MB 133 Digital Files
      - Provost: 7/19/06 @ 1 PM Science Library Rm 223 portrait: James Anderson, 2006 July 31; 84.2 MB 43 Digital Files
      - Criminal Justice: 7/28/06 @ 2 PM Draper 219 portraits: David Bayley, Janet Stamatel, and Marvin Krohn, 2006 August 9; 140.6 MB 90 Digital Files
      - NERFI: 8/16/06 @ 9:30 AM Bio / Forensics Labs NERFI Brochure / Poster photos, 2006 August 30; 652.2 MB 368 Digital Files
      - School of Criminal Justice: 10/6/06 @ 3:30 pm Empire Commons to Standish Room for Albany Symposium on Crime and Justice., 2006 October 9; 220.2 MB 116 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: 9/27/06 @ 12:30 PM Biology 125, 2006 October 10; 90.9 MB 51 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: 12/13/06 @ 1 p.m. Advisement Services Center for photo of Whitney Sperrazza and her advisor, Kimberly Kerker., 2006 December 14; 99.4 MB 53 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing`: 12/6/06 @ 12 Noon Middle Earth Counselilng CTR portrait: Carolyn Ortiz, 2006 December 19; 178.8 MB 89 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: 1/8/07 @ 3:45 pm in University Hall Atrium for photo of Chris King for web feature. Photo session: 01/09/07 at 3:30 pm in the Main Library, followed directly by shots of the same group in the Campus Center Food Court., 2007 January 8; 690.8 MB 333 Digital Files
        2016 December 19 Submission Information Package (SIP) created with createSIP.py version 0.1
      - Media & Marketing: 2/7/07 at 11 AM, location TBA for photo of Minjeong Kim for Campus Update., 2007 February 8; 106.4 MB 153 Digital Files
      - Jewish Studies: 5/4/07 @ 12 Noon - 2 p.m. Milne 200 for the 6th Annual Michael J. Hindelang Lecture., 2007 May 4; 23.2 MB 39 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: 5/15/07 @ 8:30 - 9:30 AM in the atrium of UNH for photo of Moscow Delegation for Campus Update., 2007 May 15; 48.6 MB 64 Digital Files
      - School of Criminal Justice: 6/12/07 @ 10 AM Draper 105, School of Criminal Justice for photos of faculty members Julie Horney, Diana Mancini, Robert Apel and Shawn Bushway., 2007 June 12; 39.3 MB 103 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: Prof. Stamatel and Erin Horan photo for web feature here in UAB 201 on 9/7/07 at 9:30 a.m., 2007 September 21; 49.5 MB 99 Digital Files
      - History: 2 sessions- one is at 9 am on 9/19/07 for Lauire Kozakiewicz (head shot) in the well area, 2nd fl of Ten Broeck and the second is @ 2 p.m. same location for Richard Fogarty, David Hochselder and Kendra Smith-Howard (head shots)., 2007 September 21; 20.8 MB 39 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: 11/15/07 from 1:30 - 2:30 at the NYSP Forensic Investigation Center to take a button shot of student Danielle Conklin for home page. Pat is need to art direct., 2007 November 23; 45.4 MB 111 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 11/14/07 @ 2 PM Life Sciences Bldg. Alex Shekhtman's Lab w/ three grad students: Shadakshara Swamy Puttamadappa, Jingjing Xie, and Andres MacDonald Web project, 2007 November 28; 41.0 MB 94 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: photo sessiion: 1/25/08 @ 2:30 pm location TBA Dian DeFelice / Fence, 2008 February 7; 39.0 MB 93 Digital Files